{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_Hibbert_Tupper",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Charles Hibbert Tupper is Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871430993080139,
            "question": "Is 'Sir' part of Charles Hibbert Tupper's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9870854020118713,
            "question": "What is the full name of Charles Hibbert Tupper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9808664321899414,
            "question": "What is the surname of Charles Hibbert Tupper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9724920988082886,
            "question": "How many names are in Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9685240983963013,
            "question": "What is the middle name of Charles Hibbert Tupper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.962895929813385,
            "question": "Is 'Charles' the first name of Charles Hibbert Tupper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9605074524879456,
            "question": "What is the first name of Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9296809434890747,
            "question": "What title precedes Charles Hibbert Tupper's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9288784861564636,
            "question": "What title does Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8073065280914307,
            "question": "Does Charles Hibbert Tupper have a knighthood?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Charles Hibbert Tupper is Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4587_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title does Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper hold?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4587_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title precedes Charles Hibbert Tupper's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4587_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the first name of Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4587_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4587_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the full name \"Sir Charles Hibbert Tupper\" for Charles Hibbert Tupper, indicating his knighthood and surname."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}